The world's hottest undercover agents are back!
Hard Hunted is a action, thriller film directed by Andy Sidaris.
A nuclear trigger has been smuggled to the Middle East by an evil mastermind named Kane, and the weapons
could upset the delicate balance of power in the region if they fall into the wrong hands.
It's up to three bombshell federal agents to avert
disaster and restore the precarious balance.
Donna Hamilton, played by Dona Speir.
Nicole Justin, played by Roberta Vasquez.
Bruce Christian, played by Bruce Penhall.
Kane, played by Geoffrey Moore.
Lucas, played by Tony Peck.
Edy Stark, played by Cynthia Brimhall.
Hard Hunted is a 1992 action/adventure film starring Dona Speir, Roberta
Vasquez,  Cynthia Brimhall, Bruce Penhall and Geoffrey Moore.
It was directed and written by Andy Sidaris.
It's the seventh installment in the  Triple B film series.
The film explores themes of hawaii, federal agent, psychotronic.
The tone is intense.